# Fahmi Ali Husni

Banyuwangi, East Java, Indonesia

✓ fahmiali130499@gmail.com

\(\cdot+6282131715623\) in https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahmialihusni/

### **SUMMARY**

Experienced in web developer, especially in frontend and ui/ux designer. I am currently continuing my 7th semester of Informatics majoring at the University of Muhammadiyah Malang and have a passion for development and technology such as coding, research, and competitive programming.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Frontend Engineering Intern**

PT. Singhasari SEZ - SEAL

July 2022 - Present, Malang, Indonesia

- I am using the Next.JS framework with the Typescript programming language
- Slicing the UI design into the website
- Using the CSS framework with TailwindCSS and UI Components with Flowbite
- State management with Redux
- Using the Fetching API with Axios
- Progress management with Trello

#### Frontend Engineering Student - KAMPUS MERDEKA YABB & GoTo

February 2022 - July 2022, Jakarta, Indonesia

- · I learned FrontEnd by using ReactJs
- Create Spotify playlists using Spotify Developer with React technology using TypeScript language
- Implementing UI components using react components, such as react bootstrap and implementing styling tailwind css
- · Spotify playlist can search songs, create, edit and delete playlists

## Input Data for Covid-19 Vaccine Student Events

**UIN Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang** 

September 2021, Malang, Indonesia

• Vaccine data input

## **React IS for Web Development** Digital Talent Scholarship - KOMINFO

· Make a website calculator · Create a to-do list website May 2022 - 25 June 2022, Indonesia

## **ORGANIZATION**

### **Informatics Student Association**

**University of Muhammadiyah Malang Informatics** 

• Information & Communication ( INFOKOM )

February 2022 - July 2022, Malang, Indonesia

### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Muhammadiyah Malang

**Informatics Engineering** 

• Software Engineering

# **PROJECT**

### Web Developer

• WordPress Personal Blog (www.projectfa.com)

- FAL Food Store (https://fal-store.netlify.app/)
- MyPortfolio (https://fahmiali.netlify.app/)
- Web Fullstack Service(http://widduserviceeee.herokuapp.com/)
- Web Design Competetion HimitPens Surabaya (https://botnet-web.netlify.app/)
- Web School Company Profile and Registation Online in Elementary 1 Watukebo (https://sdn1watukebo.sch.id/)
- Calculator Website (https://fahmiali99.github.io/calculator.github.io/)
- Leaf Classification (https://image-klasifikasi-daun.herokuapp.com/)
- Spotify Playlist (https://fal-music.vercel.app/)
- SIPP Kota Batu (https://sipp-dev.vercel.app/)

September 2019 - Present

September 2019 - Present

UI / UX Design October 2019 - Present

- YGuide App Mobile
- Ambul App Mobile
- Booklogia Web App
- Botnet Web App
- Widdu Service Web App

### **SKILLS**

Programming Language: PHP, Java, C++, C, Python, Javascript,

TypeScript, Dart

Framework: Webpack, Laravel, ReactJs, NextJs, VueJs, Flutter

**Styling : Bootstrap, Tailwind Css** 

UI Component : React Bootstrap, Chakra, Material UI

Design Photo: Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD

Video Editing: Adobe Premiere Pro, Vegas, Filmora

Audio Editing: Cubase 5, FL Studio, Pro Tools